ful Greasy
We'll be checking Oh Yeah, Yeah, Yeah
Playing Oh Yeah, Yeah, Yeah
So It's you
Awesome in good luck
acompañes
you know thewow ever
Hey, if you wanna win, you gotta play it smart
You got to lose the chance, the wise will take it all
Hey, I see the hell is that you're gone
Sorry, can't be good, it's all gone
Handlawnしてく, it's the end of thought
I'm gonna die, high, she don't move
You're right, when all is good
You're right, if you wanna play
Time isして,時はもう満ちた
We're shooting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Flavoring, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,結晶とした光を色さ解放する
We're shooting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Flavoring, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,逆転と栄光のそう
We're shooting, your運命, we'll have to go
See? It all worked out
Yeah, maybe I overreacted just a bit
Well, Aranella is a goddess
She knows better than to take a human life like that
And Seiya is capable of handling just about anything by himself
I wish I could be as level-headed as you, Aria
It's so weird, you'd think I'd know Seiya better by now, but I don't
Well, I could only make an informed guess because you talk about him non-stop
Speaking of which, let's change the subject
Hey there, Mosh
You mind showing Rista what you've been up to?
Um, sure
Oh, what did you do?
I released one of his dragon metamorphosis seals
By gaining a dragon appendage, his attack power has jumped several levels
Yeah! You like that? Pretty cool, right?
Well, you said cool, I say kind of creepy
But it's yours, so...
What's so creepy about it, Rista?
I know, right? By itself, it's awesome, but with the rest of him, meh, not so much
What's wrong with the rest of me? Tell me how you really feel!
That's not very nice, you two
Mosh has worked very hard to achieve his special skill
The comically colossal dragon claw
What is this, bust Mosh's balls, Dave?
Mosh, you really need to slow your roll
Why you little cute bird
Okay, also pretty creepy
You're so dead
Wait, I recognize this spell
Yes, it's support magic that slows an opponent down
Delay
No way!
The dormant power you sensed in A-Lulu was support magic?
Correct?
Fix this!
Speed me up!
Okay, fine!
Let's turn things up a notch
You knew what I meant at, Lulu, and this was not it!
You've had your buzz up, take me back already!
Is that what this is up?
She can also cast haste?
When did she learn one spell, much less its counter?
She acquired these new talents fairly recently
I suspect your desire to help others was the cause of this exciting development
Do you understand the more that's coming out of my health?
No, because it's faster than the speed of sound!
Yes, I think delay and haste are just what Saiyan needs for support
Good work, both of you
Why does the sadist get all the damn praise?
I expect to see both of you again sometime
By then, A-Lulu will know more magic
And Mosh, you'll have mastered your dragon metamorphosis
Right!
Yep, I can hardly wait!
Oh, I would have come to you sooner if I'd known you could help boost their strength like this
Everything you've done has had a purpose
Thanks to the experience these two had gained
Their talents were able to blossom beautifully
Yeah, we're gonna be tough to beat
Especially with Saiyan's new bow abilities
Did you just say bow?
Please don't tell me
Midas isn't the one teaching him this time around, is she?
Yes, only the best for Saiyan
And I'm pretty sure she's the only archery goddess
How could you be so stupid if that woman is utterly terrifying?
You mean like even more terrifying than Adanella?
The two don't compare in the slightest and that's putting it mildly
Do you know why she was banished to live in the Divine Forest?
She's a nymphomaniacal goddess that will prey on any heroes summoned
If they cross her path, she abducts and sexually devours them
Sexually?
It's the reason Ishtar drove her out into the forest
Allowing men anywhere near her is absolutely forbidden
But they're just training
I swear I saw it myself
Midas must be savoring her quarry and waiting till the last day
I bet she's ready to explode
Oh no, no
Sexual relations between a goddess and a human are forbidden
He won't come back from this
It's a one and done situation
One and done?
For a stupid hookup?
What are you still doing here?
Go find Saiyan this instant and step on it!
I refuse to allow my one and a hundred million hero to get booted for Divine Booty
Unless it's my Divine Booty
I took it back! I take that back!
If I twist my ankle running in witches, he is gonna pay!
Saiyan!
So, you guys just hanging out or...?
I mean, she is
She asked me to give her ten minutes to get ready for something
Apparently, it's Bondage 101
Think of this exercise as one last test, Saiyan
Use a volley of three light arrows to score hits on these ropes
That shouldn't be too challenging for you
Oh! So this is like a final exam for all of your training
But Frankie!
If you succeed, my naked body will be released
You will then catch me and learn from my vast carnal knowledge
Vast, huh? That's a weird flex
I've been patient
These past three days have been nothing but torture
Especially with the man as handsome as you are
Hit me!
Do it, Saiyan!
Release me from these ropes and then release me again with your body!
Sounds messy
Saiyan! Step away from the nympho!
Don't nympho-boss me
You're a call, but remember succeeding means letting her sloppy bits go free
I'm not worried
Saiyan! You just distrenched right in her face!
I realize she's immortal and all, but you just don't go for the head like that!
Have you lost it?
Oh, Saiyan, that's not the kind of foreplay I had in mind
Here's a bondage tip
Never put yourself in a position you cannot escape
No, sir! Eyes off!
If I were to give a grade for that last shot, it would be a failing one
I hope you're ready for your retest
Saiyan, pull out!
Now then, prepare yourself because I'm going to attack
Try to stop me, I dare you
Think of this as a more intensive and hands-on part of your training
Mega training is not a thing! Please stop!
Ready?
Three shot shining arrow
I threw up in my mouth
Goddesses do not die!
You can't stop me no matter how hard you are
Uh, do all goddesses have a side like this?
Pretty sure she's a demon in disguise
Get your lost eyes off, Mosh!
An appetizer before the main course sounds divine
I like them when they're young
The age is just a number after all!
Come on, Mosh! She's gone from heaven!
First I'll strip you down
Then I'll lay you down
And finally I'll wear you down until you're too exhausted to me!
I knew taters would be your next target
Someone as thirsty as you will drink just about anything
Five shot shining arrow for her pleasure
To be penetrated so many times
I don't know what any of her words mean
It's weird, what pain makes you happy?
Uh-uh, not appropriate!
That was amazing
I'm completely spent
Seeing you shoot five shots in a row
And made me in a glorious way
You're the best I've ever had, Seiya
I am perfectly prepared
I am 100% ready for this
If I never see that vulgar goddess again
It will still be too soon
Wait, why is it so quiet?
Ah, so you've returned
Captain Rosalie decided to head off toward the fly's lair by herself
What? Why'd she do that?
I mean, we said we'd be right back
Bart and the others are going after the captain on horseback
We should follow them immediately
So predictable
It's only been an hour
I highly doubt she's running a trash breath yet
It's possible
Chill, bro
We'll catch up to her
We'll keep a look out here
Perfect location!
We can see them and their lair
But they can't see us!
Huh?
It's her!
She's an idiot!
A brave idiot, but still
An idiot
That's Light's blessing, which must be one of her skills
It's protecting her from those mob attacks
She just became the perfect decoy
Cool, now I can snipe Beetleface
You predicted this?
That's why we came here instead of going straight for Rosalie
You know, you can swap more flies with honey and whatnot
Aw, crap
Way to go, Rista
Huh?
What did I do?
Flies have an exceptional sense of smell
They came over because you're stinking up our lookout with your goddess Stink
What dick would that be?
You're joking, right, Sam?
Do you guys smell anything?
Uh, you don't smell that strong today
Not enough to be super concerned about
So I do stink?
How I'm losing
Fucking old lady's laundry
All of you, shut up
It's all or nothing
I'm going for a headshot
Can you do it?
That was the lamest question ever
Oh, look, we found the hero
We were wondering if you would ever show up
Mister, please, will you be quiet?
The flies will hear us
I offer you my sincerest apology
Now you're being even louder, dude
I hate to bring it to you, master
But those flies are gunning straight for us
Stay calm
I'm still on it
I was ready for something like this to happen
I'm Rosalie Roseguard
The War Master's daughter
Hey, Beelbub
Come and give me a fair fight
What'd she think?
Stop!
Not a problem
Saw that coming, too
I'm starting to wonder if there's anything you've done
Didn't see coming
You stupid fly jerk
Let me go!
Did your psychic powers tell you
The War Master's daughter would get taken hostage?
My boom!
Sweet charity
I get you're frustrated
But don't take it out on the ladies
I'm not
I just lost my decoy
And I need another one
Go be useful for once
Um, you want me to be a decoy?
I got a plan
You have to buy me some time, though
You're really putting me on the spot here
How am I supposed to distract them?
You could say
Nice weather we're having, huh?
Just like that
Remember
Don't take your eyes off what's-her-face
If you can do that, we'll be good
Okay, fine!
I'll clear a pathway for you
Don't worry, Stinky
Just fly
Oh, right
Thanks for the backup
And would you please stop calling me Stinky?
Stop right there!
Huh?
Judging from those wings, you must be a goddess
If you're on gear branday, that means you have that meathead hero with you
Yeah, well, he wanted me to relay a message
Let her go!
Not to worry
I was just using this girl as bait to lure the hero out
Wait, you're seriously gonna release her?
Yes, but only once I'm considerably higher
In honor of your hero's downfall, I'm preparing a reverse firework
Any thoughts?
Is this not an excellent hype for you to make a beautiful firework?
I'm gonna make you apologize for the men you killed if it's the last thing I do!
Considering you're about to join those men, I'd say you're in no position to demand apologies
You bastard!
That's enough!
Your hero said he would be back by now
Is he still training?
Not in front of the bug!
Huh?
Training?
That means he's planning to attack me with a bow and arrow
Oh, well, that's just great!
He's a psychic too!
Guess I'll have to gain more altitude to really set this one off!
He's flying higher, so magic arrows have no chance of hitting him!
Way to be the worst distraction ever, Rista!
He he he!
Now to treat myself to the sight of you exploding into tiny red and pink pieces!
Hmm, I'll have to fling you to the ground as hard as I can so she can't catch you!
If he throws her with all his strength, I'll never catch her!
Hey, coward!
Get back on the ground and fight me like a man!
I'm not a man, I just dress like one!
The only thing you'll be fighting is gravity!
Ah, I'm out of options!
Ah!
Huh?
So, nice weather we're having, huh?
Life above the clouds, am I right?
Um, what are you talking about?
Uh, I have no idea!
Anytime now, Seiya!
Ah!
Gotcha!
Whoa, didn't factor in the weight of your armor!
It's pretty heavy, but I think we're gonna be okay!
Sorry about that.
That was Shining Arrow.
Somehow Seiya managed to reach him, but...
Doesn't make any sense!
Even magic arrows don't have that range!
I've done my research, and it's not possible!
Oh yeah? Why is that?
I factored in the effective trajectory when I flew this high up!
I don't care what magic arrows he's using, there's no way they could span such distance!
My hero is one in a hundred million, bub!
Get used to disappointment!
However gifted he is, it's still unlikely.
He doubtlessly flew after us until he was close enough to fire off a shot!
Like a stalker outside a window, he's hiding somewhere in the clouds as we speak.
His brain may be fly-sized, but he's just as perceptive as Seiya.
I am the fastest of all the Demon Lord's forces in the air!
You may call me the Lord of the Skies!
I have no clue where you are, Seiya, but you better not miss him again!
Oh, hero! I would exceedingly like to see your bow skills!
I won't even hide from you!
Scale of one to ten, how confident are you in your stupid hero right now?
Um, I'd say a ten?
I mean, he said that cheesy line...
Seven lights? Is that a seven-shot shining arrow?
He's trying to one-up the goddess of freaking archery!
It can't be avoided!
He he he he! Rolling dodge!
He evaded all seven!
No! Is this when we lose Seiya?
Kei and Brandi is basically the ultimate difficulty level!
There you are!
I'm coming, hero!
Seiya, watch out! You're no match for him in the air!
He he he he!
That hurts!
Holy...
Oh...
This bites!
Huh?
Are those magic lights or magic birds?
That kind of technique definitely belongs to Seiya!
But when did he use it?
I get it.
Once Beelbub dodged the arrows, they became birds and flew back like a boomerang!
I think you're right!
I bet it has a ridiculous name like Transform Automatic Garuda!
That's why Seiya!
Damn you!
I'm gonna be the firework now!
Ah!
What goes on in that beautiful head of his?
Even though he outdid Meet Us by two arrows, he made a backup attack just in case they missed!
Seiya Ryukyuan, the only guy tough enough to save Gei Brandi, while staying cautious every step of the way!
And looking damn fine doing it!
Thank goodness you're safe, Captain Rosalie.
Yeah.
Master!
That was fan-freaking-tastic!
It really was! That bug brain didn't stand a chance!
Hey, hotshot! Pretty slick move! The Transform Automatic Garuda!
What are you babbling about now?
Oh, sorry!
That's just a silly name I came up with.
So what's it called? You know, that move when your light arrows turn into birds and ricochet back!
Oh, you're referring to Boomerang Birdie Boom Boom.
What? That's awful! You can't seriously call it that!
I didn't think of it until just this second.
Ugh! Gray, feel free to use my name if you want.
I don't want to. It's way too long and stinks as bad as you do.
You're so mean! Nothing about me stinks!
The title of hero doesn't suit you. Your victory was anything but chivalrous.
A true hero is someone who strikes down his foe without trickery. Just like my father does.
Now look! Rosalie, the only reason you're standing here right now is because of Seiya!
You could at least thank him! A little help here? Just try not to be offensive.
Nothing I say will make a difference, so let's drop it.
Barky just likes the sound of her own words.
What was that?
She's losing it again!
Whether it's shooting arrows or slinging insects, Seiya's lethal in everything he does.
Okay. Time to take out the remaining flies.
Tater Tot, short stack. Let's see what you're made of.
Really? They're letting the kids take the reins? That's so sweet of you!
It's not like I'm blind or anything.
I can tell they've been training and have not only leveled up, but also gained abilities.
No! We have!
It's true!
Pop to it. I want to see maximum effort out there.
I'll make you proud! Wait and see!
Yeah! Wait and see!
Wait and see!
Nice.
Faster!
I feel betrayed. So very betrayed.
You're up, short stack. Speed Tater's up with your haste magic.
Oh, sure.
Perfect. Now use dragon hands to collect fly corpses.
Okay, cool.
Nice.
This method is much more efficient. It's also really entertaining me.
I feel betrayed. I feel betrayed. So very betrayed.
You're up, short stack. Speed Tater's up with your haste magic.
Oh, sure.
Perfect. Now use dragon hands to collect fly corpses.
Okay, cool.
Nice. This method is much more efficient. It's also really entertaining me.
Good enough. I'll take it from here.
Cast Hell's Fire!
Am I a dragon or a maid?
I don't even know what to say to them in this situation.
Eliminating the stragglers? Isn't that beneath you, hero?
I'm not the biggest fan of your attitude, so you can take it with you when you leave!
Captain Rosalie, we need to tell them about the you-know-what before we go.
I was getting to that, okay?
God!
We may not see eye to eye, but there's something you should know.
Hmm?
Listen up. In a shrine near the village of Isale, there is a suit of armor.
This legendary armor will help you defeat the demon lord.
I'm sorry, it's legendary?
Not just legendary. Ultimate.
It was crafted by an ancient sage who foresaw our current crisis.
Our plan was to inform the hero as soon as he appeared, but the fly sidetracked us.
The knights of Rosegard have kept watch over the years, justly protecting the sacred treasure.
You all must be grateful, and I really can't blame you.
Sounds sketchy. Real sketchy.
Are you positive it's not cursed armor?
How could anyone curse it if it was always being watched? It wouldn't be sacred anymore!
Never know. The armor could be cursed, sacred, and legendary at the same time.
Yes, there is!
How can someone as irritating as you be dubbed a hero?
That armor should be worn by a gallant and noble man who's proven himself like my father.
YAH!
Oh! Please excuse us, Mr. Hero!
Before anything else, I say we go to that village and snag this armor.
And maybe get some rest while we're at it.
I could use a break from naked goddesses and fly monsters.
Yeah, a nap sounds pretty good to me.
Whatevs.
I use some MP for my magic bow.
I say we stop at the end so we can recharge.
Oh, Joy!
No, but we were just here.
They leveled an entire village.
Hey, look! Over there!
That's the item shop!
We have to help!
Well, well, we meet again, hero.
You can sheathe your sword since I'm the one who summoned this creature.
Huh?
It's an Adamantois.
A gargantuan demon I brought forth from a whole other world.
Hey, P-Pants.
If you're going to call me a name, I prefer you use...
Summon or kill Kapoor.
One of the four heavenly kings.
We've got supplies from one of the four heavenly kings?
Thanks to my crystal ball, I've been observing you and your motley crew bearing witness to your adventures.
You've had your fun, but I think you've meddled in Gaya Brande long enough.
That humongous turtle! That's why you summoned it!
You're trying to take out Ziya!
You assume much, though you were right in one regard.
Adamantois is here for a reason.
And that's the reason?
Yes. The sacred armor is now nothing more than a pile of scraps.
It was made from adamantite, the strongest metal in Gaya Brande.
Ordinarily, no one would be able to break it.
No! Come on!
I destroyed the armor before you could get your filthy human hands on it.
Just our luck. We're all for two in the legendary equipment department.
Hero.
Unlike most mortals, you had a slim chance of defeating the demon lord.
But I guess we'll never know for certain since your journey ends here.